This looks like carded wool, a
carded wool coat, but it's actually
100% recycled plastic.  It was
done as with carded wool techniques
.   I
actually never would have said that.
The same material is spun with the
worsted spinning wheel and this is always
recycled plastic on the wool spinning wheel
, but then if we put it on the
cotton spinning wheel it
looks like cotton.   It
looks like cotton.  And if we then put it
on the silk spinning wheel
, it
looks like silk.  And then we
also started putting it on garden cars,
so they become the bomber jackets.
This bomber jacket is beautiful.
And then you always see plastic, but
they all look like traditional wool.
This is all plastic,
just recycled plastic.